moshimoshi-nippon.jp 2016-12-06

# PRIVACY POLICY | もしもしにっぽん | MOSHI MOSHI NIPPON

ASOBISYSTEM Company Limited, full name of the applicable legal entity here (hereinafter referred to as “Our company”, “we” or “us”), respects your privacy. Please note that we own and operate this website “Moshi Moshi Nippon” (hereinafter referred to as “Our website”). Our website will maintain your Personal Information so carefully and sensibly. We will only share Personal Information collected through the platform as described in this policy, unless we provide you with choices. Specifically, we may share your Personal Information.

Our website is operated by the following guidelines to protect your privacy.

### 1\. Personal Information

(i) The types of Personal Information we may obtain are:  
– your first and last name – your birthday  
– your home address – your phone number  
– your email address  
– your contact address  
(ii) Histories and Characteristic Information  
We collect and store all of the additional information that you provide to us in your profile.  
This may include, among other information:  
– your tracking pixels  
– your site usage  
– your ZIP code  
– your gender  
– your job  
– your ID history  
– your IP address  
– your Cookies  
– your Mobile device unique identifier

### 2\. How We Use The Information We Collect

We may use the Personal Information we obtain about you to:

(i) We may use your contact information to send you our email magazines.  
(ii) We may use your contact information to send you notifications regarding our campaign.  
(iii) We may use your contact information to respond to user support requests.  
(iv) We may use your Personal Information to show each target promotional content or ads on our website based on the Personal Information the users made available our website.  
(v) We collect statistical information about how people use our website. Some of this information is derived from Personal Information, such as your location, age and sex. We use this information to improve our customer service. (vi) We may use your contact information to detect violating terms of service of our website, or to address fraud.  
(vii) We may use your contact information to other services on our website.

### 3\. Disclosure of personal information to third parties.

We do not disclose your Personal Information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. 

(i) We may disclose Personal Information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety.  
(ii) Such information will be disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable laws and regulations, legal process or governmental request.   
(iii)In case that disclosure is required by other regulations.  
(iv) In case that the user applies for seminars or events organized by the third party through our website or us, and receives requests for information from the third party  
(v) The user purchase products or services from us or the third party, and receives requests for information from the third-parties or logistics services providers. Authorized third-parties or transportation companies with which we may report information about your account, including information on late payments, missed payments.  
(vi) In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets associated with our website, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.  
(vii) We disclose any information as it reasonably believes is necessary to satisfy our users.

### 4\. Web Cookie Policy

We use cookies to measure behavior on this website.  
Cookies are small computer files that a website places on an Internet user’s computer to store basic information for usability purposes and to save choices made on some pages.  
As a general rule, cookies help website operators serve their users better and more quickly. The cookies used on this website do not identify you personally.

### 5\. Disclaimer

(i)You may share Personal Information with others through chat, text, email or communications features. We encourage you to carefully access of any services.  
(ii) This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, content sources, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through our website, or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services.

### 6\. A person in charge of information management

We accept responsibility for your profile information.  
Yusuke Nakagawa (President, ASOBISYSTEM Company Limited )  
UP-buildings, 3-29-3, Jingumae, Shibuya-ku, Tokyo #150-0001

### 7\. How To Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about our practices regarding Personal Information or about this Privacy Policy, please submit your request to  
moshimoshi-info@asobisystem.com

### 8\. Note

We may revise this statement at any time. We will post any revisions to this policy, and the changes are effective when we post them here. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
